F#Fade_BG#1
NULL#It's mid-afternoon. The sun shines so brightly.#0
NULL#You watch people walk as you sit on a chair in the middle of a shopping district.#0
NULL#While wathcing peoples minding their own bussiness, you just remembered that you haven't had lunch yet.#0
NULL#And so, you are hungry.#0
NULL#You stand up and start wondering around to find a place to eat.#0
NULL#Nothing really catch your eye, until you reach the end of the shopping district.#0
NULL#You saw a small board standing in front of a door made of glass#0
NULL#Cafe Lajoie.#0
NULL#You don't recall seeing this place before.#0
NULL#Maybe it has only been opened just recently?#0
NULL#You decided to have lunch in this place.#0
F#Fade_BG#0
F#Play_Clip#1
00_Miyuki#"Welcome to Cafe Lajoie"#0
F#Play_Music#0
NULL#As you walk through the door, you are greeted by the waitress who waited in front of the door#0
NULL#Long grey hair and blue eyes. You don't meet such features much these days.#0
NULL#With a radiant smile the waitress welcome you inside the cafe.#0
00_Miyuki#"Table for one, right? Would you like the smoking or non-smoking section?"#0
NULL#The waitress asked you in which section you wish to be dining.#-1
F#Selection#2
S#"Smoking Area"#25
S#"Non-Smoking Area"#93
00_Miyuki#"Very well, please follow me"#0
NULL#You walk to your table with the waitress guiding you there#-1
NULL#You sat on the chair the waitress guided you to#-1
00_Miyuki#"Here is our menu."#0
NULL#The waitress handed you the menu.#0
00_Miyuki#"Excuse me, but I will be leaving you now."#0
00_Miyuki#"Just call me when you have decided what to order."#0
NULL#The waitress left you. You open the menu to see what they are serving.#-1
NULL#It turns out that they don't really serve much food.#-1
NULL#They only had 2 main dishes, which are Curry Rice and Ramen noodle.#-1
NULL#A pretty standard food for a lovely place like this.#-1
NULL#Not to mention this place name, Lajoie. In French it translates to The Joy.#-1
NULL#You're not sure you feel any joy coming out from this place#-1
NULL#Perhaps it's because you're the only one here at this moment.#-1
NULL#Well, we shouldn't be too quick to judge.#-1
NULL#With so little option you can choose, you decide to call the waitress to take your order.#-1
00_Miyuki#"Yes, may I take your order?"#0
F#Jump_to_Line#45
00_Miyuki#"Ergh... sorry, but we don't have that."#0
00_Miyuki#"Something else that I can get you?"#0
F#Selection#3
S#"Curry Rice"#49
S#"Ramen Noodle"#51
S#"WAAAAFFFLEEEESSS!!!!!"#43
00_Miyuki#"Curry Rice it is then."#0
F#Jump_to_Line#52
00_Miyuki#"Ramen Noodle it is then."#0
NULL#The waitress writes your order in her order book.#0
00_Miyuki#"I will bring your order as soon as it's ready"#0
00_Miyuki#"Now, if you excuse me"#0
NULL#And so, she left you once again.#-1
NULL#Aside from the lack of food variety they have here, everything else are impressive.#-1
NULL#The waitress is especially good with her job serving.#-1
NULL#You feel genuinely welcomed and treated like well distinguished guest.#-1
NULL#When I think about it, is this what people call maid cafe?#-1
NULL#Though not obvious, her dress reminds you that of maids in those kind of cafe#-1
NULL#Now then , it's time you wait for your meal to come.#-1
NULL#You casually open your phone, trying to distract yourself.#-1
F#Fade_BG#-1
NULL#And so you wait.#-1
NULL##-1
F#Fade_BG#0
00_Miyuki#"Thank you for waiting. here is your order"#0
NULL#The waitress sets your meal above the table.#0
NULL#By the smell and the look of it, you will be having a good lunch.#0
00_Miyuki#"Enjoy."#0
NULL#There's nothing left to say, time to chow down.#-1
F#Fade_BG#-1
NULL#The food is good.#0
NULL#You ended up devouring your food.#0
NULL#You just can't help yourself by the deliciousness of the meal you're eating.#0
F#Fade_BG#0
NULL#Without you realizing it, you have finished your food.#0
NULL#You didn't want to stay too long, so you call the waitress for your check.#0
00_Miyuki#"How were your food? I hope you like it."#0
00_Miyuki#"Anyway, here's your bill. You can pay it at the cashier"#0
NULL#Without thinking much, you head straight to the cashier to pay your bill#-1
F#Fade_BG#-1
NULL##-1
F#Fade_BG#0
00_Miyuki#"Please come again."#0
NULL#As you walk toward the exit, the waitress opened the door and says farewell.#0
NULL#It was not much, but it was a refreshing experience eating here.#-1
F#Fade_BG#1
NULL#As you take a step outside, you wonders.#-1
NULL#...#-1
NULL#Maybe I should come here more often#-1
F#Jump_to_Line#250
00_Miyuki#"Very well, please follow me"#0
NULL#You walk to your table with the waitress guiding you there#-1
NULL#You sat on the chair the waitress guided you to#-1
00_Miyuki#"Here is our menu."#0
NULL#The waitress handed you the menu.#0
00_Miyuki#"Excuse me, but I will be leaving you now."#0
00_Miyuki#"Just call me when you have decided what to order."#0
NULL#The waitress left you. You open the menu to see what they are serving.#-1
NULL#It turns out that they don't really serve much food.#-1
NULL#They only had 2 main dishes, which are Curry Rice and Ramen noodle.#-1
NULL#A pretty standard food for a lovely place like this.#-1
NULL#Not to mention this place name, Lajoie. In French it translates to The Joy.#-1
NULL#You're not sure you feel any joy coming out from this place#-1
NULL#Perhaps it's because you're the only one here at this moment.#-1
NULL#Well, we shouldn't be too quick to judge.#-1
NULL#With so little option you can choose, you decide to call the waitress to take your order.#-1
00_Miyuki#"Yes, may I take your order?"#0
F#Jump_to_Line#113
00_Miyuki#"Ergh... sorry, but we don't have that."#0
00_Miyuki#"Something else that I can get you?"#0
F#Selection#3
S#"Curry Rice"#117
S#"Ramen Noodle"#119
S#"WAAAAFFFLEEEESSS!!!!!"#111
00_Miyuki#"Curry Rice it is then."#0
F#Jump_to_Line#121
00_Miyuki#"Ramen Noodle it is then."#0
NULL#The waitress writes your order in her order book.#0
00_Miyuki#"I will bring your order as soon as it's ready"#0
00_Miyuki#"Now, if you excuse me"#0
NULL#And so, she left you once again.#-1
NULL#Aside from the lack of food variety they have here, everything else are impressive.#-1
NULL#The waitress is especially good with her job serving.#-1
NULL#You feel genuinely welcomed and treated like well distinguished guest.#-1
NULL#When I think about it, is this what people call maid cafe?#-1
NULL#Though not obvious, her dress reminds you that of maids in those kind of cafe#-1
NULL#Now then , it's time you wait for your meal to come.#-1
NULL#You casually open your phone, trying to distract yourself.#-1
00_Miyuki#"..."#0
NULL#You sense the waitress staring at you while you're not looking#0
NULL#She is standing not far from where you are sitting#0
NULL#You don't really feel any bad intent from her, perhaps there's something she wanted to say to you#0
F#Selection#2
S#"What is it?"#138
S#"Yes?"#138
00_Miyuki#"Urgh... sorry..."#0
NULL#She walk toward your table to get closer to you#-1
00_Miyuki#"Sorry, did I bother you?"#0
F#Selection#2
S#"Not really"#144
S#"A bit"#144
F#Play_Music#-1
00_Miyuki#"I-I see..."#0
00_Miyuki#"..."#0
NULL#...#-1
F#Play_Music#1
00_Miyuki#"We don't often have customers come here, especially at this hour"#0
00_Miyuki#"It can be lonely, you know"#0
NULL#Well, this is new#0
NULL#You're not sure if this is okay.#0
NULL#As her briliant smile turn slightly sadder, you feel as she is a completly different person.#0
NULL#Since you didn't know what to do, you just let things happen#0
00_Miyuki#"I'm glad that you came here today. I really do."#0
00_Miyuki#"I know it's weird cause we never met before."#0
00_Miyuki#"But thank you..."#0
00_Miyuki#"..."#0
NULL#...#-1
NULL#This is the time when you are suppose to say something#0
F#Selection#3
S#"What?"#165
S#"Get lost!"#165
S#"I LOVE YOU"#165
NULL#Since you don't have the BALLS to actually said that, you ended up only nodding to her#0
NULL#In reply, she smiles back to you#0
F#Play_Music#-1
NULL#And just like that, she smiles again like when you just came here#0
NULL#You're not really sure what just happen, so you just shruged it off#0
00_Miyuki#"Hey..."#0
00_Miyuki#"Do you want to play with me?"#0
00_Miyuki#"You know... until your food ready?"#0
NULL#The thougth of declining her crossed your mind#0
NULL#Of course, you don't want to act like an asshole, so you accepted her offer#0
F#Play_Music#0
00_Miyuki#"Great"#0
00_Miyuki#"Let's go~~!"#0
NULL#And just like that, you decided to play with her#-1
F#Play_Music#-1
NULL#Although you are not even sure about what is going on#-1
F#Change_Scene_With_Pref#3
F#Fade_BG#0
F#Play_Music#0
00_Miyuki#"Yay, you finished the game"#0
00_Miyuki#"How was it? Did you enjoy it?"#0
F#Selection#3
S#"Yes, actually"#190
S#"It was fine"#193
S#"Could have been better"#196
00_Miyuki#"Right, right?"#0
00_Miyuki#"I'm glad you enjoyed it"#0
F#Jump_to_Line#198
00_Miyuki#"Eeh... Is that so?"#0
00_Miyuki#"Well, you don't dislike it, I guess it's okay."#0
F#Jump_to_Line#198
00_Miyuki#"Ugh.. Why though?"#0
00_Miyuki#"I was hoping you would enjoy it"#0
00_Miyuki#"..."#0
00_Miyuki#"Say..."#0
00_Miyuki#"It maybe a bit too much."#0
00_Miyuki#"Can I call you "Master"?"#0
00_Miyuki#"You know, like in maid cafes..."#0
F#Selection#2
S#"Sure"#206
S#"Yes, but tell me your name first"#207
00_Miyuki#"Yay, now I have a Master"#0
00_Miyuki#"Oh, I forgot. I haven't introduced myself haven't I?"#0
00_Miyuki#"My name is Miyuki."#0
00_Miyuki#"Starting today,I will be at your service, Master"#0
NULL#You're not really sure how things turn out the way it is#0
NULL#But you just acquired yourself a personal maid#0
NULL#At least, in here#0
NULL#Miyuki huh?#0
NULL#It may feel a bit awkward remembering the circumstances#0
NULL#But you accepted her with an open hand#0
00_Miyuki#"Ah, it appears your lunch is ready"#0
NULL#Miyuki stands up and walk toward the window between the dining floor and the kitchen#-1
NULL#Walking back here, she brought with her the food that you ordered#0
00_Miyuki#"Here you go, Master"#0
NULL#As Miyuki set up your plate, you can see how she carefully put your dish#0
NULL#You can notice how her thoughtfulness translated to your dining experience here.#0
00_Miyuki#"Enjoy your meal, Master"#0
NULL#For a second you forgot why you're here in the first play#0
NULL#It's time to eat up#-1
F#Fade_BG#-1
NULL#The food is good.#0
NULL#You ended up devouring your food.#0
NULL#You just can't help yourself by the deliciousness of the meal you're eating.#0
F#Fade_BG#0
NULL#Without you realizing it, you have finished your lunch#0
NULL#Even thought it was a simple dish, it tasted like something you never had before.#0
NULL#You called Miyuki to get the check#0
00_Miyuki#"How was your meal, Master?"#0
00_Miyuki#"Anyway, here's your bill. You can pay it at the cashier"#0
NULL#Without thinking much, you head straight to the cashier to pay your bill#-1
F#Fade_BG#-1
NULL##-1
F#Fade_BG#0
00_Miyuki#"Please come again, Master."#0
NULL#As you walk toward the exit, Miyuki opened the door and says her farewell.#0
NULL#You wave at her and gave her a smile.#0
NULL#Eating out here today really refreshed your mind.#-1
F#Fade_BG#1
NULL#As you take a step outside, you wonders.#-1
NULL#...#-1
CC#MiyukiChapter#1
NULL#When will I got a chance to meet her again#-1
F#Play_Clip_No_Wait#0
NULL#Congratulations, you have unlocked Miyuki's Chapter 1#-1
NULL#Tap to Continue...#0
F#Change_Scene_No_Pref#5