NULL#Midday. Lunch time#-1
F#Fade_BG#1
NULL#You wander around the shopping district to find something for lunch.#-1
NULL#But all shop already crowded with people.#-1
NULL#Your stomach also begun to grumble.#-1
NULL#It's a very hot day, and there are a lot of people here.#-1
NULL#You start wander round again until you at the end of shopping district#-1
NULL#"Is there any place to eat that are not too crowded?"#-1
NULL#"Maybe I'll just go grab something from the convinience store"#-1
NULL#Just before you enter the convinience store, you saw a small board standing across the walkway.#-1
NULL#'Cafe Lajoie'.#-1
NULL#You don't recall anything about this cafe.#-1
NULL#Maybe because this cafe had only opened recently or you didn't notice it at all.#-1
NULL#...#-1
NULL#And so, you decide to go have lunch there.#-1
F#Fade_BG#0
F#Play_Clip#1
F#Play_Music#0
00_Miyuki#"Welcome to Cafe Lajoie"#1
NULL#When you open the door, the cafe's waitress greets you.#0
00_Miyuki#"Good afternoon"#2
NULL#Judging by her appearance, she is around 17 years old.#0
NULL#You can sense a naive vibe around here.#0
NULL#It's not so rare to see such young girl working on a cafe nowadays.#0
NULL#On the other hand, her blonde hair and blue eyes, it's very rare around here.#0
NULL#Perhaps she's a foreigner?.#0
00_Miyuki#"Table for one,right?"#2
NULL#"Yes, thank you".#0
NULL#You follow her to the table#-1
NULL#She waits until you sit, as she give you the menu#0
00_Miyuki#I'm sorry, but I'll be leaving you for a moment.#2
00_Miyuki#Just call me when you are ready to make your order.#2
NULL#She left you to go to the back.#-1
NULL#As you open up the menu, you noticed that there's not a lot of option.#-1
NULL#Omelette and fried rice, that's it.#-1
NULL#As for the drink, they only serve orange juice and white coffee#0
NULL#What a weird combination you thought#0
NULL#"Well, might as well try right?"#0
NULL#You decide to call the waitress to take your order#0
00_Miyuki#"Yes, may I take your order?"#2
F#Selection#3
S#"Omellete+ Orange Juice"#52
S#"Fried Rice + White Coffee"#54
S#"One of your smile."#45
00_Miyuki#"Hahaha..."#1
00_Miyuki#"I'm sorry sir, I'm afraid your choice of order is unavailable at this moment".#8
00_Miyuki#"Consider ordering something else, dear sir".#3
NULL#Says her with a smile in her face.#0
NULL#The vibe of naivety you felt moments before went out the window just like that.#0
NULL#Clearly she knows what's going on.#0
F#Jump_to_Line#41
00_Miyuki#"Omelette with Orange Juice it is then"#3
F#Jump_to_Line#55
00_Miyuki#"Fried Rice with White Coffee it is then"#3
NULL#The waitress wrote down your order#0
00_Miyuki#"I'll bring your order as soon as it's finished"#2
00_Miyuki#"Now, if you excuse me"#2
NULL#And so, the  waitress left you alone.#-1
NULL#Sitting in a lonely chair, inside a lonely cafe.#0
NULL#Well, this is what you wanted in the first place.#0
NULL#Escape from reality, solace beneath the walls of solitude.#0
NULL#Well, this is what you wanted in the first place.#0
00_Miyuki#"Excuse me..."#2
NULL#The waitress suddenly reappeared in front of you.#0
00_Miyuki#"I see you are very lonely"#2
00_Miyuki#"Your order won't be finished any time sooner"#2
00_Miyuki#"So, why don't play a little game while we wait?"#1
00_Miyuki#"Of course, if you don't mind..."#2
F#Selection#2
S#"Sure, why not."#104
S#"Sorry, I'll pass."#72
00_Miyuki#"Ah... is that so"#5
00_Miyuki#"My bad then, I'll be going now"#7
NULL#The waitress left you, again.#-1
F#Fade_BG#-1
NULL#Now, you wait for your food to come.#-1
NULL##-1
F#Fade_BG#0
00_Miyuki#"Thank you for waiting. here is your order"#1
NULL#The waitress sets your meal above the table.#0
NULL#By the smell and the look of it, you will be having a good lunch.#0
00_Miyuki#"Enjoy."#2
NULL#There's nothing left to say, time to chow down.#-1
F#Fade_BG#-1
NULL#The food is good.#0
NULL#You ended up devouring your food.#0
F#Fade_BG#0
NULL#Without you realizing it, you have finished your food.#0
NULL#You didn't want to stay too long, so you call the waitress for your check.#0
00_Miyuki#"How were your food? I hope you like it."#2
00_Miyuki#"Anyway, you can head to the cashier if you want to pay"#3
NULL#Without thinking much, you head straight to the cashier to pay your bill#-1
NULL#...#-1
00_Miyuki#"..."#3
NULL#Turns out she also works as the cashier here#-1
00_Miyuki#"Please come again."#1
NULL#As you walk toward the exit, the waitress opened the door and says farewell.#0
NULL#It was not much, but it was a refreshing experience eating here.#-1
F#Fade_BG#1
NULL#As you take a step outside, you wonders.#-1
NULL#...#-1
NULL#Maybe I should come here more often#-1
F#Jump_to_Line#156
00_Miyuki#"Great, let's begin"#1
NULL#In your mind, you don't really want to do this.#0
NULL#But judging on how things are going, you might as well try it.#0
F#Change_Scene_With_Pref#3
F#Fade_BG#0
F#Play_Music#0
00_Miyuki#"Yay, you finished the game"#1
00_Miyuki#"How was it,sir? Did you enjoy it? Do you want to play again?"#4
F#Selection#2
S#"It was fun, thanks"#118
S#"I'm still not satisfied, I want to play again."#115
00_Miyuki#"Certainly, let's play again"#1
NULL#And so, you play again.#-1
F#Jump_to_Line#107
00_Miyuki#"Glad to hear that.#1
NULL#It was pretty surprising that you got a chance to play while waiting for your food.#0
NULL#It was nice, for a change#0
00_Miyuki#"Ah, wait here. Your food should be ready by now.#4
NULL#The waitress left you to get your order#-1
00_Miyuki#"Thank you for waiting. here is your order"#1
NULL#Shortly after that, she is back with your meal on a tray#0
NULL#The waitress sets your meal above the table.#0
NULL#By the smell and the look of it, you will be having a good lunch.#0
00_Miyuki#"Enjoy."#2
NULL#There's nothing left to say, time to chow down.#-1
F#Fade_BG#-1
NULL#The food is good.#0
NULL#You ended up devouring your food.#0
NULL#You just can't help yourself by the deliciousness of the meal you're eating.#0
F#Fade_BG#0
NULL#Without you realizing it, you have finished your food.#0
NULL#You didn't want to stay too long, so you call the waitress for your check.#0
00_Miyuki#"How were your food? I hope you like it."#2
00_Miyuki#"Anyway, you can head to the cashier if you want to pay"#3
NULL#Without thinking much, you head straight to the cashier to pay your bill#-1
NULL#...#-1
00_Miyuki#"..."#3
NULL#Turns out she also works as the cashier here#0
00_Miyuki#"Please come again."#1
NULL#As you walk toward the exit, the waitress opened the door and says farewell.#0
NULL#It was not much, but it was a refreshing experience eating here.#-1
F#Fade_BG#1
NULL#As you take a step outside, you wonders.#-1
NULL#...#-1
NULL#What was the waitress' name again?#-1
CC#MiyukiChapter#1
F#Play_Clip_No_Wait#0
NULL#Congratulations, you have unlocked Miyuki's Chapter 2#-1
CB#FWUnlocked#1
F#Play_Clip_No_Wait#0
NULL#You can also now play Food Wars in Free Mode#-1
CCG#RewardArray#0
F#Change_Scene_No_Pref#1