NULL#Midday. Lunch time#-1
F#Fade_BG#1
NULL#"Ah... It's so hot today."#-1
NULL#Why did this have to happen to a girl like me?#-1
NULL#Out of nowhere, my friend asked me out for lunch today at the shopping district.#-1
NULL#I haven't gone out lately, I prefered staying at home on weekends.#-1
NULL#We were suppose to meet at the new cafe that just got opened...#-1
NULL#...until someone texted me just now.#-1
NULL#"smthing came up, can't go, next time maybe, sorry lol"#-1
NULL#How dare she canceled on me just like that!? #-1
NULL#It took me an hour just to get here...#-1
NULL#...#-1
NULL#It would be a waste to come back home now.#-1
NULL#I'm starting to get hungry anyway.#-1
NULL#It's not like I hate eating alone or anything.#-1
NULL#...#-1
NULL#Anyways, here I stand in front of the place we were suppose to be eating at.#-1
NULL#'Cafe Lajoie'#-1
NULL#A very lonely place, no one is eating inside.#-1
NULL#I step inside through the wooden door.#-1
F#Fade_BG#0
F#Play_Clip#1
F#Play_Music#0
NULL#A very different atmosphere from before.#-1
NULL#Stinging sunray turned into cooling air conditioner.#-1
NULL#A whole new world awaits.#0
01_Mizuo#"Welcome."#1
NULL#A man wearing chef uniform stand in front of me.#0
NULL#Even thought he said welcome to me, his face says otherwise.#0
01_Mizuo#"You're alone right? Please follow me. I'll lead you to your seat."#1
F#Selection#2
S#"Oh why, thank you."#34
S#Don't take his offer#38
01_Mizuo#"You're welcome."#2
NULL#He lead in front of me and take me to my seat.#0
NULL#Though he talked with a grateful voice, he didn't smile in a slightest.#0
F#Jump_to_Line#40
NULL#How rude, thinking I couldn't find a seat on my own.#0
NULL#I choose not to follow him, instead I sit at a table near the door I just went through.#-1
01_Mizuo#"Here's the menu."#1
NULL#The waiter handed me the menu.#0
01_Mizuo#"Well, I'll leave you alone for now."#1
01_Mizuo#"Call me when you are done choosing"#1
NULL#He walks back, standing behind the kitchen window waiting for my order.#-1
NULL#I opened up the menu, only to realize there's not much to order#-1
NULL#Omelette and fried rice, that's it.#-1
NULL#As for the drink, they only serve orange juice and white coffee#0
NULL#"Now that's weird"#0
NULL#I could just got out now if I want. But that would defeat the reason why I came here in the first place.#0
NULL#...#0
NULL#I call the chef to finally take my order.#0
01_Mizuo#"You done? What will you have today?"#1
F#Selection#3
S#"Omellete+ Orange Juice"#63
S#"Fried Rice + White Coffee"#65
S#"WAFFLEEEE"#57
01_Mizuo#"Ah, it appear someone has been watching too much of Dane Cook lately."#7
01_Mizuo#"I regretfully inform you that we have yet to sell any waffle to this point."#3
01_Mizuo#"If you're kind enough, please order something that are in the menu."#2
NULL#It appears I manage to annoy the chef for a bit.#0
NULL#And who's this Dane Cook he was talking about?#0
F#Jump_to_Line#53
01_Mizuo#"Omelette and Orange Juice? Okay."#1
F#Jump_to_Line#66
01_Mizuo#"Fried Rice and White Coffee? Okay."#1
01_Mizuo#"I'll make your order now, so wait for a moment."#1
NULL#The chef left me as soon has he finished writing the order I made.#-1
NULL#I open my phone in effort to pre occupy myself.#0
F#Fade_BG#-1
NULL#And so I wait...#0
NULL#I hope the food come as soon as possible.#0
NULL#The atmosphere here is dead.#0
NULL#...#0
F#Fade_BG#0
01_Mizuo#"Thank you for waiting, here's your food."#1
NULL#The chef bring my food to the table.#0
NULL#Luckily, it didn't took long enough before I completely lost hope.#0
NULL#On top of that, he also set up the plate right in front of me.#0
NULL#What a nice man...#0
NULL#...#0
NULL#Wait, ofcourse he's just doing his job right?#0
NULL#What am I thinking?#0
01_Mizuo#"Eat up, you don't wanna to eat it while it has already become cold."#2
NULL#There's nothing left to say, I start eating #-1
NULL#...#0
NULL#The food is good.#0
NULL#The taste of it really wakes up my taste bud that I thought has already been dead for a long time.#0
NULL#Been a while since I eat food that repelish my soul.#0
01_Mizuo#"..."#1
NULL#I couldn't help but noticed that the chef is staring at me eating, while sitting at a table not far from here.#0
NULL#Not that it's creepy or anything, doesn't he got anything else to do?#0
NULL#Hm...#-1
F#Selection#2
S#Ignore him#96
S#"Yes?"#108
NULL#He can look all he want, It won't make me budge a bit.#-1
NULL#...#0
NULL#Before I realize it, I finished the food I was eating.#0
NULL#After wait for a bit, I headed to the cashier so I can pay the bill.#0
NULL#...#0
NULL#And leave immidiately, since I don't have anything else to do there.#0
F#Fade_BG#1
NULL#As I step outside, the heat of the outside world touch my skin again.#0
NULL#Ever hot, never pleasent.#0
NULL#...#0
NULL#I headed back to my apartement as I end my uneventful day.#0
F#Change_Scene_No_Pref#1
01_Mizuo#"Ah..."#2
NULL#He heard me calling out to him.#-1
NULL#As the result, he walk towards my table.#0
01_Mizuo#"I apologize if I bothered you."#1
01_Mizuo#"I couldn't help but notice that you are eating alone by yourself"#1
01_Mizuo#"No one does that, especially at a place like this."#1
01_Mizuo#"So, did your friend canceled out on you or something?"#2
F#Selection#2
S#"How do you...?"#118
S#"Yeah, kinda..."#118
01_Mizuo#"Ah, I was right then..."#5
01_Mizuo#"I really hated those kind of people..."#5
01_Mizuo#"I'm sorry you have to went through that."#3
NULL#For some reason, he said sorry to me.#-1
NULL#Not sure he's really feel apologetic, or just condecending and do it out of pity.#0
01_Mizuo#"You don't mind if I sit here?"#1
NULL#Instinctally I nodded. There's not much reason why I shouldn't allow him to sit with me.#-1
NULL#Also, I'm not in no position to decline, as he managed to see through me.#0
01_Mizuo#"Great."#1
NULL#He take a seat on the chair in front of me.#-1
01_Mizuo#"Ah, I believe I haven't introduced myself yet."#2
01_Mizuo#"Call me Mizuo, as you see I'm the cook here."#1
01_Mizuo#"Pleased to meet you."#1
NULL#He take a seat on the chair in front of me.#0
NULL#At first glance, I thought he would be the "bad boy" kind of guy.#0
NULL#Turns out he's quite a good person.#0
01_Mizuo#"Ah, you're almost done."#1
01_Mizuo#"Wait a sec, I got something."#1
NULL#Something? I wonder what it is.#-1
NULL#He put his hand into his pocket, and then showed me something that appears to be some kind of a card deck.#0
01_Mizuo#"I want to play something with you."#1
01_Mizuo#"It's called High and Low card game."#1
01_Mizuo#"Basically you only have to guess whether one card has higher or lower value than the last one."#2
01_Mizuo#"It's a bit hard to explain now, I'll tell you everything you need to know as we play..."#1
01_Mizuo#"...Assumming you want to play."#3
01_Mizuo#"So, what do you say?"#1
F#Selection#2
S#"Sure, let's play."#152
S#"No, thanks."#147
01_Mizuo#"Ah, it's a no then?"#3
01_Mizuo#"Well, I'm sorry to bother you. I guess I'll go back to the kitchen then."#2
NULL#Mizuo left and went back to the kitchen.#-1
NULL#...#-1
F#Jump_to_Line#99
01_Mizuo#"Great, let's start then."#1
NULL#And so, I tag along and play with Mizuo.#-1
F#Change_Scene_With_Pref#4
F#Fade_BG#0
F#Play_Music#0
01_Mizuo#"Ah, you managed to finished the game."#1
01_Mizuo#"Good for you"#2
F#Jump_to_Line#166
F#Fade_BG#0
F#Play_Music#0
01_Mizuo#"Too bad, you went backrupt."#1
01_Mizuo#"Better luck next time"#7
01_Mizuo#"..."#7
01_Mizuo#"I am terribly sorry, that was uncalled for."#3
01_Mizuo#"How was it, did you enjoyed our game?"#1
F#Selection#3
S#"Yes, it was fun."#171
S#"It was okay."#173
S#"I dont quite enjoy it."#175
01_Mizuo#"Ah, glad you like it. Thank you"#2
F#Jump_to_Line#176
01_Mizuo#"Okay? Okay then."#2
F#Jump_to_Line#176
01_Mizuo#"Is that so? I sincerely apologize."#3
01_Mizuo#"..."#1
NULL#Mizuo started staring at me without saying a word.#0
NULL#It seems he has something to say.#0
NULL#...#0
01_Mizuo#"Well, guess I'll head back to the kitchen."#2
01_Mizuo#"Don't wanna make boss angry."#2
01_Mizuo#"Though there's no new customer after you."#3
NULL#Ah, now that he mentions it, he's right.#0
NULL#There are no new customers in sight.#0
01_Mizuo#"It's not new though, there aren't many customers at this time too."#1
01_Mizuo#"I leave you now, have a good day."#1
NULL#Mizuo left and went back to the kitchen.#-1
NULL#...#-1
NULL#There's nothing left to do here, might as well go to the cashier now and head back home.#-1
NULL#...#-1
01_Mizuo#"..."#2
NULL#As I walk toward the cashier, I saw Mizuo standing in the kitchen through a window just behind the cashier.#-1
01_Mizuo#"..."#1
NULL#I think he noticed me standing in front of the cashier.#-1
01_Mizuo#"Hey."#1
NULL#He called out to me as I finish paying my bill.#-1
01_Mizuo#"Thank you for coming today, see you later."#2
NULL#As he said his farewell, I walk towards the entrance door#-1
NULL#It was not much, but eating out here has been quite the experience.#-1
F#Fade_BG#1
NULL#I'm starting to wonder.#-1
NULL#...#-1
NULL#When will I ever meet with him again?#-1
CC#MizuoChapter#1
F#Play_Clip_No_Wait#0
NULL#Congratulations, you have unlocked Mizuo's Chapter 2#-1
CB#HnLUnlocked#1
F#Play_Clip_No_Wait#0
NULL#You can also now play High And Low in Free Mode#-1
CCG#RewardArray#3
F#Change_Scene_No_Pref#1